[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "Question": "What is the maximum possible length of an identifier?",
        "option1": "16",
        "option2": "32",
        "option3": "64",
        "option4": "None of these above",
        "Ans": "None of these above"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "Question": "Who developed the Python language?",
        "option1": "Zim Den",
        "option2": "Guido van Rossum",
        "option3": "Niene Stom",
        "option4": "Wick van Rossum",
        "Ans": "Guido van Rossum"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "Question": "Which one of the following is the correct extension of the Python file?",
        "option1": ".py",
        "option2": ".python",
        "option3": ".p",
        "option4": "00",
        "Ans": ".py"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "Question": "Which of the following type of a variable is volatile?",
        "option1": "Mutable variable",
        "option2": "Dynamic variable",
        "option3": "Immutable variable",
        "option4": "all type variable",
        "Ans": "Mutable variable"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "Question": "In which language is Python written?",
        "option1": "PHP",
        "option2": "English",
        "option3": "C",
        "option4": "all of these",
        "Ans": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "Question": "Which character is used in Python to make a single line comment?",
        "option1": "/",
        "option2": "//",
        "option3": "#",
        "option4": "!",
        "Ans": "#"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "Question": "When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do:",
        "option1": "Shows a warning",
        "option2": "Ignores the statements",
        "option3": "Prompts to complete the statement",
        "option4": "Throws an error",
        "Ans": "Ignores the statements"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "Question": "What is the method inside the class in python language?",
        "option1": "Object",
        "option2": "Function",
        "option3": "Attribute",
        "option4": "Argument",
        "Ans": "Function"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "Question": "Which of the following declarations is incorrect?",
        "option1": "_x = 2",
        "option2": "__x = 2",
        "option3": "__xy__ = 2",
        "option4": "None of these",
        "Ans": "None of these"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "Question": " Which of the following is not a keyword in Python language?",
        "option1": "val",
        "option2": "raise",
        "option3": "try",
        "option4": "map",
        "Ans": "val"
    }
]